They ought to make the day the time
changes the first day of summer.
What?
Well, it's eight o'clock
and it's still light.
A lot of good
the extra daylight does us.
Now we've still got
a three-hour drive back.
We're not going to be home
until after midnight.
Well, if it really bugged you,
Johnny, you wouldn't do it.
You think I wanna blow Sunday
on a scene like this?
You know, I figure we're either
gonna have to move mother out here,
or move the grave into Pittsburgh.
She can't make
a trip like this.
I don't know that she can't.
- Is there any candy left?
- No.
Look at this thing.
"We still remember. "
I don't. You know,
I don't even remember what the man I
Johnny, it takes you five minutes.
5 minutes to put the wreath on the grave
and 6 hours to drive back and forth.
Mother wants to remember,
so we trot 200 miles into the count
and she stays at home.
Well, we're here, John, all right?
Radio: Testing... back on...
Ah, ladies and... We're coming back
on the air after an interruption
due to technical problem...
There's nothing wrong with the radio.
Must've been the station.
Which row is it in?
There's no one around.
Well, it's late.
If you'd gotten up earlier...
Oh, look, I already lost
an hour's sleep in the time change.
I think you complain
just to hear yourself talk.
There it is.
I wonder what happened
to the one from last year.
Each year we spend
good money on these things.
We come out here, and the
one from last year is gone.
Well, the flowers die,
And the caretaker
or somebody takes them away.
Yeah, a little spit and polish,
he can clean this up sell it next year.
Wonder how many times
we bought the same one?
Hey, come on, Barb,
church was this morning, huh?
Hey, I mean,
praying's for church, huh? Come on.
I haven't seen you
in church lately.
Well, there's not much
sense in my going to church.
Do you remember one time
when we were small, we were out here?
It was from right over there.
I jumped out at you
from behind the tree
And grandpa got all excited, and
he shook his fist at me, and he said,
"Boy, you'll be damned to hell. "
Remember that?
Right over there.
Well, you used
to really be scared here.
Johnny.
- Well, you're still afraid.
- Stop it now. I mean it.
They're coming to get you, Barbra.
Stop it. You're ignorant.
They're coming for you, Barbra.
Stop it. You're acting like a child.
They're coming for you.
Look! There comes one of them now.
- He'll hear you.
- Here he comes. I getting out of here.
Johnny!
Help me!