They ought to make the day the time
changes the first day of summer.
What?
Well, it's eight o'clock
and it's still light.
A lot of good
the extra daylight does us.
Now we've still got
a three-hour drive back.
We're not going to be home
until after midnight.
Well, if it really bugged you,
Johnny, you wouldn't do it.
You think I wanna blow Sunday
on a scene like this?
You know, I figure we're either
gonna have to move mother out here,
or move the grave into Pittsburgh.
She can't make
a trip like this.
I don't know that she can't.
- Is there any candy left?
- No.
Look at this thing.
"We still remember. "
I don't. You know,
I don't even remember what the man I
Johnny, it takes you five minutes.
5 minutes to put the wreath on the grave
and 6 hours to drive back and forth.
Mother wants to remember,
so we tro
Hey, come on, Barb,
church was this morning, huh?
Hey, I mean,
praying's for church, huh? Come on.
I haven't seen you
in church lately.
Well, there's not much
sense in my going to church.
Do you remember one time
when we were small, we were out here?
It was from right over there.
I jumped out at you
from behind the tree
And grandpa got all excited, and
he shook his fist at me, and he said,
"Boy, you'll be damned to hell. "
Remember that?
Right over there.
Well, you used
to really be scared here.
Johnny.
- Well, you're still afraid.
- Stop it now. I mean it.
They're coming to get you, Barbra.
Stop it. You're ignorant.
They're coming for you, Barbra.
Stop it. You're acting like a child.
They're coming for you.
Look! There comes one of them now.
- He'll hear you.
- Here he comes. I getting out of here.
Johnny!
Help me!