Ravana was the evil king of Lanka
and he just stole Sita.
He was an incredibly learned man.  From what I understand, Ravana was...
Actually the only bad thing he seems to have done...
...is capture Sita.
Which is kind of interesting because everything else about him seems to be, like
he was this really learned guy,
he knows all these weapons
he prays to the right Gods...
so all this stuff! He's like this Good King.
Except that, over time, we've been led to believe he's this complete...
that he's like Mogambo.
That's right, he lived on an island also!
He was a devoted Shiva-bhakta.
and he plays -
-all these instruments...
Veena with his intestines.
With his intestines?
Yeah, for Shiva.
There's this whole thing about how devoted a fan he was
and he's asking Lo
aster. Rama is powerful.
Sister, do not bother me with your petty concerns.
Dear Brother Ravana, have you seen Rama's wife Sita?
She is the most beautiful woman in the world.
Her skin is fair like the lotus blossom.
Her eyes are like lotus pools.
Her hands are like, um, lotuses.
Her breasts like big, round, firm, juicy...
Lotuses!
Mmmm, ahhhh...
Make Sita your wife, Ravana. Steal her from Rama!
Don't do it, Master!
I'll hear no arguments from you, Mareecha. You must help me at once.
Transform yourself into a beautful golden deer to distract Rama.
While Sita is unguarded, I'll grab her!
Sita WILL be mine! Hahahahahaaa!
What a beautiful golden deer!
Oh Rama, won't you capture it for me?
I don't know, Sita. It could be a tri