Ravana was the evil king of Lanka
and he just stole Sita.
He was an incredibly learned man.  From what I understand, Ravana was...
Actually the only bad thing he seems to have done...
...is capture Sita.
Which is kind of interesting because everything else about him seems to be, like
he was this really learned guy,
he knows all these weapons
he prays to the right Gods...
so all this stuff! He's like this Good King.
Except that, over time, we've been led to believe he's this complete...
that he's like Mogambo.
That's right, he lived on an island also!
He was a devoted Shiva-bhakta.
and he plays -
-all these instruments...
Veena with his intestines.
With his intestines?
Yeah, for Shiva.
There's this whole thing about how devoted a fan he was