Ravana
Sister, do not bother me with your petty concerns.
Dear Brother Ravana, have you seen Rama's wife Sita?
She is the most beautiful woman in the world.
Her skin is fair like the lotus blossom.
Her eyes are like lotus pools.
Her hands are like, um, lotuses.
Her breasts like big, round, firm, juicy...
Lotuses!
Mmmm, ahhhh...
Make Sita your wife, Ravana. Steal her from Rama!
Don't do it, Master!
I'll hear no arguments from you, Mareecha. You must help me at once.
Transform yourself into a beautful golden deer to distract Rama.
While Sita is unguarded, I'll grab her!
Sita WILL be mine! Hahahahahaaa!
What a beautiful golden deer!
Oh Rama, won't you capture it fo