Ravana was the evil king of Lanka
and he just stole Sita.
He was an incredibly learned man.  From what I understand, Ravana was...
Actually the only bad thing he seems to have done...
...is capture Sita.
Which is kind of interesting because everything else about him seems to be, like
he was this really learned guy,
he knows all these weapons
he prays to the right Gods...
so all this stuff! He's like this Good King.
Except that, over time, we've been led to believe he's this complete...
that he's like Mogambo.
That's right, he lived on an island also!
He was a devoted Shiva-bhakta.
and he plays -
-all these instruments...
Veena with his intestines.
With his intestines?
Yeah, for Shiva.
There's this whole thing about how devoted a fan he was
and he's asking Lord Shiva for some wish
and, you know, he is basically playing Veena with his intestines.
It's hard to fell someone like that in battle, because
what is pain to a man who plays Veena on his intestines?
Nothing much.
What I'm really impressed with is he was the king of Sri Lanka.
No, he was the king of Lanka.
It was Lanka. It's called Ceylon. It's the same country I think.
Well the point is that's what we think.
They built the bridge.
The bridge still exists, so NASA images say.
Really? NASA? It must be true then!
Maybe they saw it when they were on the moon!
Isn't the Suruphanaka story - Suruphanaka right?
Surphanaka.
I'm messing up her name. God, they're gonna be after me
Surphanaka is the one with the really ugly nose.
Surphanaka. But she was Ravana's sister.
Ravana! Rama has slaughtered your Rakshasas in the forest. You must take revenge!
Don't do it, Master. Rama is powerful.
Sister, do not bother me with your petty concerns.
Dear Brother Ravana, have you seen Rama's wife Sita?
She is the most beautiful woman in the world.
Her skin is fair like the lotus blossom.
Her eyes are like lotus pools.
Her hands are like, um, lotuses.
Her breasts like big, round, firm, juicy...
Lotuses!
Mmmm, ahhhh...
Make Sita your wife, Ravana. Steal her from Rama!
Don't do it, Master!
I'll hear no arguments from you, Mareecha. You must help me at once.
Transform yourself into a beautful golden deer to distract Rama.
While Sita is unguarded, I'll grab her!
Sita WILL be mine! Hahahahahaaa!
What a beautiful golden deer!
Oh Rama, won't you capture it for me?
I don't know, Sita. It could be a trick!
Oh Rama, pleeeaaase?
All right, Sita. You ask for so little and give me so much.
But promise you won't leave the hut while I'm gone. The forest is dangerous.
I promise! Oh Rama, I love you!
I love you, Sita.